<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TimeTracker</string>
    
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="task_name">Task name</string>
    <string name="add_task_ok">Add task</string>
    <string name="task_name_required">The task name is required</string>
    <string name="start_time_required">The start time is required</string>

    <string name="delete_ok">Delete</string>
    <string name="delete_task_title">Delete Task</string>
    <string name="delete_task_message">Are you sure you want to delete '%s' and all of it's time records?</string>
    <string name="add_task_title">Add task</string>
    <string name="change_view_title">Change view</string>
    <string name="generate_report_title">Report</string>
    <string name="select_range">Select range...</string>
    <string name="done">Return to tasks</string>
    <string name="add_time_title">Add a new time range</string>
    <string name="delete_time_message">Are you sure you want to delete this time range?</string>
    <string name="delete_time_title">Delete Time Range</string>
    <string name="start_time_label">Start Time</string>
    <string name="end_time_label">End Time</string>
    <string name="end_not_greater_than_start">The end time must be greater than the start time</string>
    <string name="range_error_title">Time Range Error</string>
    <string name="report_title">Report for the week %s to %s </string>
    <string name="week">Week %s</string>
    <string name="title">TimeTracker (%s)</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="export_view">Export</string>
    
    
    <!-- About dialog strings -->
    <string name="version">Version %s</string>
    <string name="author">Sean E. Russell</string>
    <string name="donate"><b>If you like this app, please donate and support future development! (Click Me)</b></string>
    <string name="purpose">TimeTracker helps you record the amount of time you spend on
        activities; for example, for recording time in a time sheet at work.  It
        provides ways to view, edit, and filter times, and provides a 
        time sheet report as well.</string>
    <string name="usage_1">Create some tasks using the main task view's <i>Add Task</i> menu item.
    Tap a task to start timing; tap it again to stop timing, or tap a different task
    to switch timing to the other task.  Two tasks can not be running at the same time.
    Use the <i>Change View</i> menu item to filter the time display by a date range, such as
    viewing times for <i>Today</i>, <i>Yesterday</i>, <i>This Week</i>, etc.
    Use the <i>Report</i> menu item to view a report of the daily time sums per task
    for an entire week.</string>
    <string name="usage_2">The task context menu allows you to edit tasks (change their names), delete tasks
    (including all of the time history for that task!), or view the time log for that
    task.</string>
    <string name="usage_3">The time log for a task is filtered on the same range that you selected for the
    main task view, so if you filtered the task view for <i>This Week</i> and you open
    the time log, then you'll only see times for this week.  Use the <i>Add Time</i> to
    manually insert times into the time log.  <b>Note</b> that TimeTracker will not
    prevent you from creating times that overlap with times in other (or the same) task.
    Use the context menu for a time to edit the time range, or simply click
    on a time to do the same thing.  The context dialog for a time also includes
    the option of deleting the time.</string>
    <string name="usage_4">You can visit http://ditz.germane-software.com/TimeTracker 
    to see a list of known bugs and future enhancements.</string>
    <string name="credits_1">The TimeTracker application icon was borrowed from
    the excellent glyFX icon library by PerthWeb Pty Ltd (www.glyfx.com).</string>
<string name="export_csv_success">Successfully exported CSV to memory card as %s</string>
<string name="export_csv_fail">Failed to export CSV.  Couldn't create the file.  Is an SD card inserted?</string>
<string name="success">Success</string>
<string name="failure">Fail</string>
<string name="set_start_day_of_week">Set the day the week starts</string>
</resources>
